本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 水涟漪 刘言 熊猫大虾 魔法莉露姆
校对： Cinderella    后期： 泡面小小
我毁掉了你的文件
I destroyed your file.
但不确定那是唯一的一份
I can't be certain that's the only one they have.
如果他们发现你有前科 肯定会撤销你的签证
If they find out you've got a history, they will revoke your visa
然后遣送你回国
and they will send you home,
有前科的人是不允许获得学习签证的
because people with histories don't get study visas.
这是一个女人昨晚放在我们门口的
A woman left this at our door last night.
在你被杀的那晚它就不见了
Disappeared on the night you were murdered.
没想到现在又出现了
Now it's returned to me.
这女孩很漂亮呢
Pretty girl.
你想让我找到她的档案
You wanted me to find her file.
别着急 我们这里还有很多有趣的照片
Don't worry. We have many interesting photographs.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
弗兰克 我喜欢上别人了 我要搬出去了
Frank, I've met someone. I'm moving out.
康 你居然出卖我!
You set me up, Kang!
不然他们会吊死我的!
They were gonna hang me!
- 我们完了 - 我们早完了 山姆!
- We're done. - We've been done for a while, Sam!
我想找山姆 但他还没有回来
I was supposed to meet Sam. He hasn't come back yet.
你确定想看他这个样子?
You're sure you want to see this?
他还好吗?
Is he alright?
至少好几个小时他哪儿都去不了
He won't be going anywhere for a few hours.
最好让他在这里睡一觉
Better to just let him sleep it off here.
石龙岗之路 第一季第08集
你想谈谈这事吗?
Do you want to talk about it?
山姆?
Sam?
你看 我已经道过歉了 但你要明白...
Look, I said I'm sorry, but, you know...
- 嘿 你当时完全失去意识了
- Hey.You were completely unconscious.
又不是每天都会这样
It's not like it happens every day.
你也知道 我遇到你之后就再没碰过了
You know, I haven't touched it since we met.
但你昨晚又开始了
But you chose last night to start again.
我们说好了
We had an arrangement.
- 我们约好见面的 - 没错
- We were meant to meet. - Yeah.
你要说的就这些?
That's all you're going to say about it?
康走私炸药被抓了
Kang was caught smuggling explosives.
我意思是... 他说他是被陷害的
I mean... he said he was set up.
我信了他 结果一个无辜的人被杀害了
And because I believed him, an innocent man was shot.
为什么你不等等 和我商量一下呢?
Why didn't you wait, talk to me about it?
我们不是要一起吗?
We're together, aren't we?
当然了
Of course we are.
听着 你还打算告诉弗兰克吗?
Listen, you still plan on telling Frank?
山姆! 辛普森夫人
Sam! Mrs Simpson.
打扰了 有一个澳大利亚外交官在侦探所等你
Sorry, there's an Australian diplomat at the agency.
- 能等会吗? - 恐怕不行
- Can it wait? - Not really.
去吧 去吧 稍后我再来找你
Go, go. Um... I'll come back later.
郑夫人 希望你能理解
As you can understand,
这件事您必须优先处理
this has to take complete priority, Mrs Cheng.
山姆 这是澳大利亚大使馆的安德森先生
Sam. You know Mr Anderson from Australian Embassy.
- 斯图尔特 - 天哪 山姆你看起来真糟
- Stuart. - God, Sam, you look like hell.
如果我知道你来 就会花时间打理一下了
If I'd known you were gonna be here, I would've made the effort.
听说你弄丢了几个澳大利亚女孩
Heard you lost a couple of Australian girls.
什么? 不 我没有...
What? No, I didn't...
她们在一艘开往伦敦的货船上
They were on a freighter, bound for London.
安德森先生本打算去接应
Mr Anderson was to meet them
然后让她们乘飞机回国
and send them on a plane home,
但是他到了之后她们都不见了
but they were gone when he arrived.
什么时候外交官们开始关注起观光客了?
Since when do diplomats babysit tourists?
因为其中一个女孩是加里・艾奎斯特的女儿
Since one of the girls was Gary Edquist's daughter.
艾奎斯特?
Edquist?
我想他拥有你们北部国土的一半面积
I believe he owns half of your Northern Territory,
可对土地任意取舍
give or take an acre.
她当时是在货船上旅行吗?
What was she doing travelling on a freighter?
她老爸都可以买只班轮了
Dad could have bought a liner.
显然 她老爸并不知情
Apparently, Daddy did not know.
干得不错呢
Well, good for her.
我们还是告诉她老爸只在乎他的生意算了!
I mean, come on, tell her old man to mind his own business!
这样问题就解决了 哈?
Problem solved, huh?
轮船靠岸时这些女孩并不在船上
The girls weren't on the ship when it docked.
海关也没有她们在新加坡上岸的记录
And Customs has no record of disembarkation in Singapore.
还有她老爸是首相的密友
And her father is a close friend of the Prime Minister.
不是吧
Oh, for fuck's sake.
我们必须找到这些女孩
We have to find the girls.
卡米拉・艾奎斯特 19岁
Camilla Edquist. 19.
已被悉尼大学法律系录取
She's been accepted into law at Sydney Uni.
她朋友呢?
Who's her friend?
吉娜・克肖
Gina Kershaw.
消防局炊事员的女儿
She's the daughter of the station cook.
她们一块长大
The girls grew up together.
好吧 我们去找这个船长谈谈
Right, let's talk to this captain.
你最后一次见到她们是什么时候?
When was the last time you saw them?
晚饭时间
Dinner time.
她们像往常一样
They grabbed their food
拿了吃的到她们的船舱里去吃
and took off to their cabin, just like always.
你和她们聊得来吗? 喜欢她们吗?
Did you get on with them? Did you like 'em?
我不必和她们套近乎 她们只是付费的乘客
I don't have to get on with them. They were paying passengers.
我喜欢的是她们的钱
I like their money.
所以你也想不出她们的去向?
And you've got no idea where they could be?
不知道 问完了吗?
No. We done?
完了
Yeah.
我半小时后加燃油
I'm bunkering fuel in half an hour.
在太阳落山前开船
We cast off by sunset.
看 她们不在这儿 你满意了吧?
Oh, look, they're not here. You happy?
我们不应该去唐人街找她们吗?
Look, shouldn't we be in Chinatown trying to find them?
有人去那看过了
Someone's had a go at that.
这是什么?
What?
看来有人曾尝试把这门踢开
Looks like someone's tried to kick the door in.
你想说什么?
What are you saying?
或许什么都不是 是这船太旧了
It may be nothing. It's an old boat.
听着 大使答应了艾奎斯特先生
Look, the ambassador promised Mr Edquist
而我答应了大使
and I promised the ambassador.
- 你报警了吗? - 什么? 没有
- Did you alert the Singapore police? - What? No.
我不认为...
Look, I didn't think...
这些女孩可能只是想去城里 去观光旅游
The girls have probably just gone into town. They've gone sightseeing.
那她们为什么要带行李?
So why did they take their luggage?
大概是要待在新加坡又不想告诉其他人
Maybe they decided to stay in Singapore and not tell anyone.
所以偷偷地过了海关
Snuck past Customs.
或许吧
Maybe.
她们知道你是来带她们回国的吗?
Did they know that you were coming to send 'em home?
不知道
No.
那么 为什么她们要溜走?
Well, why did they sneak off, then?
为什么不过海关?
Why not go through Customs?
给我一小时时间 如果我还找不到她们...
Give me an hour. If I can't find them...
我马上报警
I'll call the police.
你是谁? 你想干什么?
Who are you? What do you want?
- 你是帕特丽夏・郑? - 你是谁?
- You're Patricia Cheng? - Who are you?
我是美玲 我...
I'm Mei Ling. I...
- 我们能去别处谈谈吗? - 谈什么?
- Can we go somewhere to talk? - About what?
这附近有个茶社
There's a tea house around here.
- 我有话要说... - 就在这儿说吧
- What I have to say... - You can say it right here.
我见过你丈夫... 就在他出事的那晚
I saw your husband... on the night he died.
你看到了?
Did you see it?
- 你知道发生什么事了吗? - 不知道
- Do you know what happened? - No.
然后呢?
Then what?
那晚早些时候 我们在一起
We were together, earlier in the night.
在一起?
Together?
你是他的客户... 还是朋友?
You were a client... or friend?
比朋友更近一些
More than friends.
我是在周怡家工作的时候认识他的
We met each other when I worked at Joo Ee's.
我生了他的孩子
I had his baby.
一个男孩
A boy.
已经四岁了
He's four now.
以前温斯顿抚养他
Winston used to provide for him.
可自从他死了...
But since his death...
我已经花光了所有的积蓄
I've run out of all my savings.
我没有其他人可以依靠了
I've no-one else to turn to.
你真无耻 你个下流的骗子
You have no sense of shame.You dirty liar.
那块手表
The watch.
七月份我放在你家门阶上了
I left it on your doorstep during Seventh Month.
如果你再跟着我 我就报警了
If you follow me again, I'll call the police.
大娘
Aunty.
我需要你帮忙
给我你的手
今天你想要什么消息?
What you want today?
我正在寻找两个白人女孩
I'm looking for two white girls.
山姆 小心你的小命
Samboy, your heart.
他们是澳大利亚人 从猎户星船登岸
They're Australians, off the Orion Star.
- 或许带着手提箱 背包 - 没看到
- Probably got suitcases, rucksacks. - No see.
那你有看到任何船员吗?
Have you seen any crew off the ship?
- 山姆 真为你感到难过 - 行了
- Big sadness for you, Samboy.- Yeah, OK.
你到底有没有看到船上的人?
Have you seen any crew off the ship?
我没开玩笑 我是认真的
I no joke. This serious.
我也是认真的
I'm serious too.
- 猎户星船? - 没错
- Orion Star? - Yeah.
好吧 好吧 我知道
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know, I know.
你给多少钱?
How much it worth?
快跑 快!
Run, run, run!
离开这里!
Get out of here!
他们是猎户星船的人吗?
These guys off the Orion Star?
只有那个人是
Just that guy.
先生? 在你杀了这小子之前
Gentlemen? Mind if I have a word with this bloke
介意我和他说两句吗?
before you kill him?
滚远点儿
Stay out of it.
来啊!
Come on!
- 你就是杰克? - 是啊
- Your name Jack? - Yeah.
你出现的时候 我正好恢复元气了
I just about got my second wind when you showed up.
还是谢谢你了
Thanks anyway.
没什么的 那 说说这些女孩子吧
Oh, don't mention it.So, these girls, you were saying?
好 大部分时间
Yeah. Oh, kept to themselves.
她们都自己呆着
You know, most of the time.
那剩下的时间呢?
How about the rest of the time?
你应该和霍克谈谈
You ought to talk to Hawk about that.
霍克是谁?
Who's Hawk?
就是那个手臂上有个老鹰纹身的中国小混混
Oh, mad Chinese bastard with a hawk tattoo on his arm.
亚麻色头发的那个
The blonde-haired one was all over him.
那个黑妞呢? 她有没有和谁在一起?
What about the brunette? Was she with anyone?
没有吧 至少我不知道
Nah, not that I saw.
一开始几天她们真的很友好
Oh, they were friendly enough in the first few days,
但是她们根本不知道她们来是要干什么
but they had no idea what they were in for.
你什么意思?
What you mean?
听着 你得知道... 只有他喝醉的时候
Look, you gotta understand...it's only when he drinks.
我们有证人看见你袭击了那些女孩
We have a witness who says he saw you attack those girls.
胡说
That's bullshit.
- 你有没有强暴他们? - 没有
- Did you rape them? - No.
但是你跟踪她们到了船舱里 踢门而入
But you followed them back to their cabin, kicked the door in.
没有 我不会回答你们任何问题
No. I'm not saying anything.
- 我要找律师 - 去你的律师!
- I want a lawyer. - Screw the lawyer!
- 她们到底在哪儿? - 我不知道
- Where the bloody hell are they? - I don't know.
也许她们威胁说要报警 你就让她们闭嘴了
Maybe they threatened to go to the police so you shut 'em up.
在中国南海没有人会找到她们的尸体的
No one's going to find their bodies in the South China Seas.
- 什么? - 天呐
- What? - Oh, Lord.
这太疯狂了 你一定要相信我
That's crazy.You have to believe me.
我碰都没碰她们一下
I didn't touch 'em.
那你做了什么?
Well, what did you do?
我当时喝醉了 好吗?
I was pissed. Alright?
我想进她们的船舱
I tried to get into their cabin,
但是霍克还有其他人 他们不让我进去
but Hawk and the others,they stopped me.
要是你不相信我 去问他们啊
If you don't believe me, ask them.
关于霍克你知道多少?
What do you know about this Hawk guy?
他真名叫杜坦
Real name, Do Tan.
几年前保释后消失了
Jumped bail and disappeared a couple of years ago.
街上三流小混混 与红龙帮有染
Small-time street thug.Known associate of the Red Dragons.
我负责集合船员 找到霍克 再看看他怎么说
I'll round up the crew, find Hawk,and let's see what he has to say.
汤米
Tommy.
见过这些女孩吗?
确定吗?
- 五百 数数吧 - 这是什么?
- 500. Count it.- What's this?
是你那一半股份 我买下了
It's your half of the business.I'm buying you out.
你知道吗... 有些人可以是好朋友
You know... how some people make great friends
可作为商业伙伴却很差劲?
but they're just lousy business partners?
你不应该带她去那里
You shouldn't have brought her there.
你根本不应该出现在那里
You shouldn't have been there, man.
真高兴你推荐了这个地方
You know,I'm so glad you suggested this.
我好出来跟女孩们吃吃午饭
It got me out of lunch with the girls.
哪里?
Where?
那个可怕的螃蟹餐厅 利奈特爱死了
Oh, that awful crab restaurant Lynette loves so much.
就在河那边 她说她想叫你来着
It's down on the river.She said she tried to call you.
我很久没回家了
I haven't been home much.
我离开了弗兰克
I've left Frank.
明白了
Mmm... I see.
不好意思
Excuse me.
麻烦给我两杯琴酒补剂好吗?
Can I get two gins and tonic?
特浓的 加酸橙
Doubles. With lime.
我能问问你是为了谁才离开他的吗?
May I ask for who?
一定要因为别人吗?
Does there have to be a who?
从我的经验来看 是的
Well, in my experience, yes.
山姆・卡拉汉
Sam Callaghan.
这就对了
Right.
好吧 可以理解
Well... one had speculated.
我是说 山姆 一表人才
I mean, Sam, you know, he's awfully good-looking,
充满激情 勇于冒险
he's dangerous, he's exciting.
不过从长远看 还是应该考虑弗兰克
But for the long haul,one would have thought Frank.
但是 山姆 我从来...
But, Sam, I've...
...从来没有过那样的感受...
...I've never felt anything like that...
跟任何人在一起都没有
with anyone.
克莱尔 我得承认
You've got guts, Claire.
你真有胆量
I'll give you that.
一小时之前有人把这个放在了领事馆
Someone dropped it at the consulate about an hour ago.
一万英镑 否则撕票
'￡10,000 or we kill 'em.'
直奔主题啊 是吧?
Straight to the point, isn't it?
你觉得她们现在在谁手上?
Who do you think's got 'em?
很明显啊 不是吗?
Well, it's obvious, isn't it?
海滨那片儿是谁控制的? 凯・索和他的手下
Who controls the waterfront? Kay Song and his thugs.
否则他们怎么下船?
How else did they get off the boat?
他们不会这样做的
They don't operate like that.
- 你在说什么啊? - 虎威将军控制红龙
- What are you talking about? - Tiger General runs the Red Dragons.
他们很守旧 赌钱 嫖娼
He's strictly old-school, gambling, prostitution.
他们不会绑架游客
They don't kidnap tourists.
他们现在这么做了!
They have now!
- 我们没有证据 - 这就是我需要的证据
- We have no proof.- This is all the proof I need.
我要他们搞突然袭击 找到那些女孩
I want their premises raided and the girls found.
你没这个权利
You have no authority.
很快就有了 我要正式成为你上司了
I will soon enough.I'm officially going over your head.
为什么你们这些人总以为自己知道很多?
Why do you colonials always think you know best?
- 嘿 - 好了
- Hey.- Alright.
好好
It's alright.
我爷爷很不爽
My grandfather is very unhappy.
是吗? 不爽的不只他一个
Yeah? Well, he's not the only one.
说说袭击的事吧
Tell me about the raids.
很明显 你绑架了两个澳大利亚女孩
Apparently,you kidnapped two Australian girls.
那警察为什么不这样觉得呢?
And why would the police think that?
他们被混淆了
Well, let's just say they were persuaded to the view.
有人找刺激拿枪指着他们的脑袋吗?
So someone put a gun to their head to make my life more exciting?
我想他们别无选择
I don't think they had much choice.
不要为懦弱找借口
Weakness is no excuse.
我知道是你的人绑架了她们
We know one of your men's got them.
你知道?
Do you?
叫霍克的那个混蛋
Bloke by the name of Hawk.
霍克与十三红龙无关
Hawk is no friend of the 13 Red Dragons.
实际上 他最后一次被看见是在香港
In fact, he was last spotted in Hong Kong,
可能是在跟什么老妓女翻云覆雨呢
probably catching the clap from some old prostitute.
他回到新加坡了
He's back in Singapore.
你可以帮我找到他
You could help me find him.
爷爷 我们不能袖手旁观
让这些畜生无法无天
我的父亲不会这么做
让我处理吧
这些澳大利亚人真是杞人忧天啊
Those Australians really have got their knickers in a knot.
看来他们给两个栽培者带错了路
Seems they've misplaced two of their breeders.
目前为止 新加坡在这案子里占优势
Still, with Singapore's finest now on the case,
我保证他们迟早会现身
I'm sure they'll turn up sooner or later.
要么死了 要么活着
Dead or alive.
你想见我
You wanted to see me.
坐下吧
Well, sit down.
你喝什么茶?
How do you have your tea?
我需要知道
I'll need to know.
我们还有长久的良好合作前景呢
We have many years happy collaboration ahead of us.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
你是我进入兰利的新渠道
You're my new conduit into Langley.
我估计你喜欢先加牛奶吧 是吧?
I expect you take milk in first,hmm?
你要我帮你监视中情局?
You want me to spy on the CIA for you?
我们不应该是同一个团队吗?
Aren't we supposed to be on the same team?
你到底什么想法?
What on earth made you think that?
这是莫大的荣幸啊 米勒先生
It's always a pleasure, Mr Miller.
要是传出去 你毁了一份
If it gets out that you destroyed a file
有关一个共产主义潜伏特工的文件
relating to a potential Communist sleeper agent,
而且你所作所为还是出于个人原因
and you did so for personal reasons,
受你老二的唆使
dictated by your penis,
你的前途就毁了
your career will be over.
你本国的人民很可能会吊死你
Your own people might even hang you.
当然 还有苏玲
And then... of course, there's Su Ling.
不会有美国人支持她
No America for her.
事实上 马来西亚特别支队
In fact, the Malaysian Special Branch
明天就有可能逮捕她
might even arrest her tomorrow.
你有一晚上的时间考虑
You have till tonight.
希望你能做出明智的选择
Make the sensible choice.
假如我不是中情局的一员
Imagine if I wasn't in the CIA.
那就太好了
That would be great.
假如你也不想去美国上大学
And if you didn't want to go to college in the States.
我们就可以一起逃跑了
We could just run away together.
跑去哪儿?
To where?
澳大利亚
Australia.
- 澳大利亚? - 嗯
- Australia? - Mmm.
康拉德  这样如何?
Conrad, how about this?
我们一起去美国 我上完大学取得学位
Let's go to America, let me get my degree
然后或许 我说或许 我们就结婚吧
and then maybe, just maybe, I'll let you marry me.
不行吗?
No?
这太疯狂了
Sounds crazy.
好吧 那我们就一起去看袋鼠吧
Alright, then let's go see the kangaroos.
不不不 我只是想...
No, no, no, I just thought...
想什么?
Thought what?
没什么
Nothing.
没什么 一起都会好起来的
Nothing. It's all gonna be fine.
肯定会的
Of course it will.
郑太太
Mrs Cheng.
你认识我丈夫
You knew my husband.
- 是啊 大家都爱他 - 他经常来这里
- Oh, yes. Everyone loved him. - He was here a lot.
有时他会来跟乐队一起玩
Sometimes he get up and play with the band.
我们都很想念他
We all miss him.
他认识那个这里工作过的女孩
He knew a girl who sometimes worked here?
- 美玲吗? - 是的
- Mei Ling? - Yes.
他跟她有多熟?
How well did he know her?
- 我不太清楚... - 他有没有...
- I really don't know what the... - Did he...
他有没有跟她交往?
Did he have an affair with her?
我不知道 不清楚
I don't know. Not for sure.
她说她怀了他的孩子
She says there is a child.
我要知道真相
I need to know the truth.
我不确定那是不是他的小孩
I'm not sure it was his.
但我从没见过她和别的男人在一起
I never saw her with another man.
郑太太 你还好吧?
Mrs Cheng, are you alright?
我能为你做些什么吗?
Is there something I can do?
能 离山姆远点
Yes. Leave Sam alone.
抱歉 你说什么?
Excuse me?
就算帮我个忙 回你自己丈夫身边吧
Do him a favour.  Go back to your husband.
我不能 再也不会了
I can't. Not anymore.
那就别毁了他的生活
Then don't ruin his life too.
我的价格很合理 好吗?
I think I paid a fair price, OK?
如果你还想为了几美元跟我讨价还价...
If you wanna haggle over a few dollars...
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
不是让你白帮我 我会付钱
It's not a favour. I can pay.
如果我想让两个女孩悄悄离开一艘货船
If I wanted to get two girls off a freighter unnoticed,
我要怎么做?
how would I do it?
- 多少钱? - 什么多少钱?
- How much? - How much what?
你说你会付钱 多少钱?
You said you'd pay. How much?
十块钱 这价格很合理
Ten. It's a fair price.
这叫做循环取货
It's called a milk run.
皮条客们会把妓女们带到货船上
Pimps will take the working girls out to the freighter
给那些不能上岸的船员们
for crew who can't make it ashore.
然后他们会把她们带回来的 是吗?
Then they bring them back, yeah?
好吧 - 就这样?
OK.  - That's it?
这钱赚得真容易啊
Oh, that's easy money.
我要你查出昨晚在猎户星号货船上
I need you to find out
有没有循环取货
if there was a milk run to Orion Star last night.
我还有生意要做
I got a business to run.
我觉得两个女孩子在船上被绑架了
I think two girls were kidnapped off the ship.
绑架的人是为了勒索赎金
They're being held for ransom.
你先帮我搬这些货
Help me with this first.
是谁指使你的?
Who are you working for?
什么?
What?
我丈夫被人谋杀了
Someone murdered my husband,
而你告诉我这个故事 这个捏造的故事
and now you arrive with this story, this fabrication.
是为了玷污他的名声
Is this to muddy his reputation,
好让我不去追究凶手是谁吗?
so I don't go look for his killer?
- 不是 - 你怎么拿到他的表的?
- No. - How did you get his watch?
你到底有什么目的?
What do you really want?
他根本没有情妇 是吗?
There was no affair, was there?
也没人怀孕 没有小孩 对不对?
No pregnancy? No child?
妈咪?
Mummy?
你先回去睡觉吧
妈妈等下讲故事给你听
他死的那晚 来过这里
On the night he died, he was here.
他通常在周三过来
He usually came on Wednesdays.
每周三 他都说去打麻将
Wednesdays, he played mahjong.
但是那晚我没想到他会来
But I wasn't expecting him that night.
他看上去很忧虑 甚至有点恐惧
He seemed worried, even scared.
他确信有人在跟踪他
He believed that someone was following him,
想要伤害他
that they meant to do him harm.
他走之前 给了我这块表
Before he left, he gave me the watch.
他说如果出了什么事 就把表给你
He said to give it to you, should anything happen.
我本想留着那块表 为了我们的儿子
I wanted to keep it, for our boy.
但我做不到
But I couldn't.
我没钱了
I've run out of money.
我无路可走
I've nowhere else to turn.
请你等等
Please.
他爱你吗?
Did he love you?
他爱我们的儿子
He loved our boy.
他爱你吗?
Did he love you?
他不爱我 但他爱我们的儿子
No, he didn't. But he loved our son.
他说孩子是你一直渴望得到的
He said it was the one thing that you've always wished for.
你们在一起多久?
How long?
不久 就几个晚上 仅此而已
Not long. A few nights, no more.
求你了
Please.
你尽管恨我吧 但别恨孩子
Hate me all you want, but not the boy.
那温斯顿呢?
What about Winston?
我要怎样体谅我的丈夫呢?
What do I feel for my husband?
艾奎斯特正在替我凑赎金
Edquist is wiring the ransom money to me now.
我一小时内就能拿到钱了
I'll have it in an hour.
你本可以不用惹这些麻烦的
You could have saved yourself some trouble.
我差点没渴死
Oh! A man could die of thirst around here.
多谢 安格
Thanks, Ange.
那个叫艾奎斯特的女孩怎么样了?
So, what's the latest on the Edquist girl?
- 官方消息 无可奉告 - 非官方的呢?
- Officially, no comment. - Unofficially?
去你的
Bugger off.
所以你有什么消息给我
So you got something for me,
还是我用我现有的?
or do I run with what I got?
"牧场主女儿的黑社会恐怖故事"
'Grazier's Daughter Triad Horror'.
这名字就说明了一切
This story writes itself.
我很快就回来
Back in a sec.
- 打听到什么了吗? - 一个人名
- What have you got? - A name.
他带了两个女孩出去 却带着四个女孩回来
He went out with two girls, came back with four,
还有几个船员
along with a few crew.
- 这是他带她们去的地方 - 谢谢
- This is where he dropped them. - Thanks.
嘿 要把她们带回来哦
Hey, bring them back, yeah?
你好吗?
你有见过这些女孩吗?
霍克!
Hawk!
有人吗?
Hello?
好了好了 没事了 我不会伤害你的
It's OK, it's OK, it's alright. I'm not gonna hurt you.
放轻松 冷静
Just relax, relax.
卡米拉? 我叫山姆
Camilla? I'm Sam.
我是来救你们离开这儿的
I'm going to get you out of here.
找到吉娜了吗? 她还好吗?
Have you found Gina? Is she alright?
我上上下下找遍了那里 就是不见吉娜的踪迹
I searched the place top to bottom. There was no sign of Gina.
那么卡米拉最后一次见她是什么时候?
So when did Camilla see her last?
大概两小时前
About two hours ago.
她说她们被分开关押
She said they were kept separate
这样就不能一起逃跑了
so they wouldn't escape without each other.
她在这儿吗?
Is she here?
她在跟她父亲通电话
She's on the phone with her father.
我是澳大利亚领事馆的斯图尔特・安德森
Stuart Anderson from the Australian Consulate.
很高兴看到你安全归来
We're so glad that you're safe.
爸爸 有个政府部门的人来了
Daddy, there's a man from the government here.
他想跟你通话
He wants to talk to you.
你还好吗? 你父亲呢?
You alright? How's your father?
他很生气
Angry.
不过很欣慰我没事
Glad that I'm OK.
你说船长跟这件事无关?
So you were saying the Captain wasn't involved?
不 呃...
No, um...
他曾试图...
After he tried...
我只是再也不能呆在那艘船上了
Just couldn't be on that ship anymore.
没事 我们理解
It's OK. We understand.
霍克说他会在船长眼皮子底下偷偷带我们下船
Hawk said he could get us off the ship without the Captain knowing.
他的一番话让我们觉得新加坡很给力
He made Singapore sound so exciting.
植物园里的抽彩和猴子
The Raffles and monkeys in the Botanical Gardens.
那些都是吉娜想要看的
That's what Gina wanted to see.
她会没事的 是吧?
She's going to be OK, isn't she?
山姆 我可以跟你私下说两句吗?
Sam, can I have a word?
怎么了?
Why, what's the matter?
情况很微妙 是关于艾奎斯特先生的钱
It's a delicate situation. Mr Edquist's money.
他对于这笔钱怎么花要求很明确
He's being very specific about what it can and cannot be used for.
他在说什么?
What is he talking about?
他不会帮吉娜付赎金的
He won't pay for Gina's release.
- 什么?! - 听着 我很遗憾
- What?! - Look, I am sorry.
他怪吉娜让你卷入这个麻烦
He blames Gina for getting you into this mess.
我会跟堪培拉的人谈
I will speak to Canberra.
我会试着用别的方法来筹齐这笔赎金
I will try and raise the ransom money some other way.
- 这要多长时间? - 很长
- How long will that take? - Too long.
不 山姆 这笔钱已经不能用了
No, Sam. This money is quarantined.
不要再想了
It is off the table.
安德森先生 真的有必要这样吗?
Mr Anderson, is this really necessary?
如果出了什么岔子 我有不在场证明
If things go bad, then I have an alibi.
你们从我这里偷了那笔钱
You stole that money from me.
安德森先生不和我们一起吗?
Mr Anderson not joining us?
不了 他现在很忙
No, he's tied up right now.
- 你怎么看? - 我们先看看什么情况
- What do you think? - Let's see what's going on first.
如果我们冲进去 他可能会紧张
If we bust in, he might panic.
他在屋里 里面还有其他人
He's in there with at least one other.
那是凯・索的人 我会组织突袭
That was Kay Song's men. I'll organise a raid.
她可能活不了那么长
She's not going to live that long.
- 你去哪儿? - 去试试把她带回来
- Where are you going? - To try and get her back.
嘿 山姆!
Hey, Sam!
- 嘿 - 敢碰我 你就死定了
- Hey. - Touch me, you're dead.
来坐吧 国际友人 我们有很多要庆祝的呢
Oh, come sit, my Ang mo friend. We have much to celebrate.
今天我赚了不少钱
Today I made a lot of money,
干掉了仇敌 恢复了我爷爷的名声
spilled the blood of my enemy, restored my grandfather's honour.
我都不知道要怎样感谢你
I'm not quite sure how to thank you.
告诉我那个女孩在哪
Just tell me where the girl is.
我们从不绑架白人女孩 没人跟你说过吗?
We don't kidnap white girls. Didn't anyone tell you?
那她到底在哪?
Then where is she?
这就是你的计划? 来这里向我提要求?
So that's your plan? Come in here, demand things from me.
你应该感激我没当场把你干掉
You should be grateful I don't kill you where you stand.
你刚刚还说你要谢谢我
You just said you wanted to thank me.
你没看到吗?
You don't see, do you?
我的人到的时候 你的公主正和霍克数钱呢
When my men arrived, your princess was counting money with Hawk.
坐下吃点吧
So sit and eat.
别为她流泪了
Oh, don't go shedding tears for her.
卡米拉没事 就是担心吉娜
Camilla's fine, just worried about Gina.
安德森先生情况越来越差了
Mr Anderson's gone into a steep decline.
哈 我保证他会活着
Ha. I'm sure he'll live.
我不明白 她会去哪?
I don't understand. Where would she go?
吉娜说了什么? 霍克告诉他们的地方?
What did Gina say? The places Hawk told them about?
- 是的 抽彩和... - 植物园的猴子
- Yes, Raffles and...- The monkeys in the garden.
吉娜・克肖?
Gina Kershaw?
拜托 别跑了 没事的
Please, don't run. It's alright.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是山姆 我刚刚和卡米拉在一起来着
I'm Sam. I was just with Camilla.
- 她怎么样? - 她没事
- How is she? - She's fine.
她很担心你
She's worried about you.
我知道
I know.
你跟霍克一起参与了这件事 对吗?
So you and Hawk were in this together, were you?
她是你最好的朋友 为什么你要那么做?
She's your best friend. Why would you do that?
她和我 我们计划了一年了
She and I, we planned it for a year.
我省吃俭用
I saved up every penny I had.
我们俩 一路去了伦敦
The two of us, all the way to London.
我们要告诉全世界我们能独立完成
We were going to show the world we could do it on our own.
船长袭击她以后 她一心想回家
When the Captain attacked her,she just wanted to go home.
我恳求她
I begged her.
对她来说钱不是问题
Money was never a problem for her
但我没足够的钱一个人生存
and I couldn't afford to stay on alone,
如果我回去了 我就一无所有
and if I went home, I would be left with nothing
然后我又得重新开始省吃俭用
and I would have to start saving all over again.
我们之间有约定
We made a promise to each other.
哈里森 来杯威士忌?
Harrison. Whisky?
你要我怎么做 我就怎么做
I'll do what you want.
那当然啦
Well, of course you will.
你又不傻
You're not stupid.
我想要每周一份报告
I'll expect a report, weekly,
关于在兰利总部的人的动向
on what our friends at Langley are doing.
每周五交给我 一份也不能少 明白了么?
Every Friday. Don't miss a report. Are we clear?
哈里森
Harrison.
没什么好值得羞愧的
The shame goes away.
振作起来吧
Chin up.
这下你是货真价实的间谍了
You're a real spy now.
亲爱的 你真应该跟我们一起晚餐
Oh, darling, you really should come and join us for dinner.
不行啊 弗兰克会在那的
I can't. Frank will be in there.
你不能告诉你丈夫你为了别人离开他
You can't tell your husband you've left him for someone else
然后还跟你丈夫一起吃晚餐
and then sit down for dinner with him.
- 你不属于唐人街 - 那我属于哪儿?
- You don't belong in Chinatown. - Where do I belong?
我得跟山姆在一起
I have to be with Sam.
我想跟他在一起
I want to be with him.
好吧
Alright.
那你去吧
Well, off you go, then.
好了 我把吉娜交给了斯图尔特
Well, I left Gina with Stuart.
没提绑架的事
Didn't mention the kidnapping.
我想如果他够聪明 他自己会发现的
I suppose if he's smart enough,he'll work it out for himself.
你没事吧?
You alright?
你知道吗?
Did you know?
温斯顿的外遇?
Winston's affair?
你肯定知道
You must.
我...
I...
我都不能朝他发火
I don't even get to scream at him
给他一巴掌 把他踢出家门
and slap his face and chase him out of the house.
他全家人只想让他离开我 重新开始生活
His whole family just wanted him to leave me and take a new wife.
这就是我们的文化传统
That's the way it is in our culture.
谁会要一个不能生育的女人?
Who wants a barren woman?
一切都毁了
Everything's been ruined.
好糟糕的一天
What an awful day.
克莱尔
Claire.
怎么了?
What?
我希望我们能住在一起
I wish we could live together.
塔克沃思女士觉得这不是个好主意
Lady Tuckworth doesn't think it's a good idea.
她说的没错
She's right.
行不通的
It's not going to work.
别离开弗兰克
Don't leave Frank.
这...
It's...
这里的生活不是你想象的那样
It's not a life here.
你... 你不属于这里
You don't... you don't belong here.
你还没告诉他吧?
You haven't told him yet, have you?
- 所以你仍然可以... - 没错
- So you can still... - Yes, of course.
你能理解吗?
Does that make sense?
对 理解
Yeah, it makes sense.
她被人捅了 是他干的 山姆
She's been stabbed.He did it, Sam.
他身上有血 是她的血
He had blood on him.Hers.
谋杀后逃离现场 你还有什么话要说
Any comment on getting away with murder
因为澳洲政府...
'cause the Australian government's...
- 迈卡! - 太忙了 没法
- Macca! - too busy pandering to your lot
让正义得到伸张
to see justice done.
那个人是军人!
That man's a soldier!
他杀了一个澳洲女孩
He's murdered an Australian girl.
即使他是战争英雄也帮不了他
Being a war hero will not help him.
- 太复杂了 - 她在调查毒品交易
- It's hash. - She was digging into the drug trade.
可能她调查得比迈卡想得还要深
Maybe she got further than Macca thought.
有没有可能你朋友就犯过错呢?
Is it possible you got it wrong about your friend?
可能我不想找出真相吧 可能我已经找到了
Maybe I don't want to find out.Maybe I did it.
可能除了那个没有什么可以发现了
Maybe there's nothing to find out except that.